Last year I got coal for Christmas
去年圣诞礼物是煤
I got put on Santa's naughty list (Again!)
我又进了淘气名单里(又来!)
Put a frog inside my teacher's desk – yeah, that was bad
把青蛙放进老师桌子 – 这真挺坏
But this year, I made sure I won't get missed
但今年  我确信会有礼物
Last year I got coal for Christmas (Man!)
去年圣诞礼物是煤 (啊!)
Didn't do my homework for a week (Okay, a month!)
怨我一星期没写作业(好吧  一个月!)
But now I studied hard and nearly aced most every test
但我现在努力学习每次名列前茅
So this year's Christmas better be the best
那今年圣诞别让我失望
Spent time with my old granny
陪着我的老祖母
Raking up her lawn
帮她剪草坪
Took out the garbage every night (Ewww!)
每晚还帮她倒垃圾 (噫!)
Helped mama do the laundry
帮妈妈洗了衣服
Cleaned up my room
整理房间
Did every single chore in sight – [sigh]
将眼前琐事清干净  (唉)
Last year I got coal for Christmas (Aw, shucks!)
去年我的礼物是煤 (啊   该死!)
Every photo I just made a face – [babbling]
每次拍照我都做鬼脸 (咿呀咿呀)
This year when we posed, I smiled sweetly like an angel
今年拍照时  我的笑容如天使般甜
No more taking chances just in case
以防万一绝不再冒险
Last year I got coal for Christmas (Really?!)
去年I圣诞礼物是煤 (认真的?!)
Ate dessert before my dinner most of the time (Mmm! Cake!)
在晚餐前我总想吃些甜点 (恩! 蛋糕!)
But this year I had vegetables with every single bite
但今年我每顿饭都口口不离蔬菜
I sure hope this year Santa gets it right (Come on, Santa!)
愿老人今年能给对礼物 (认真点  圣诞老人!)
Spent time with my old granny
陪着我的老祖母
Raking up her lawn
帮她剪草坪
Took out the garbage every night (She eats so much!)
每晚还帮她倒垃圾 (她吃的真多!)
Helped mama do the laundry
帮妈妈洗了衣服
Cleaned up my room
整理房间
Did every single chore in sight (Aw, gross!)
将眼前琐事清干净 (哎  烦!)
Last year I got coal for Christmas (For crying out loud!)
去年圣诞礼物是煤 (我都哭了!)
I go to bed and never brush my teeth – [exhales]
都怨我睡前从来不刷牙 (哈)
Now I bring my toothbrush each and every place I go
但现在我去哪里都牙刷不离身
So that tree better got my presents underneath
这回树下最好有我的礼物
This year, no more coal for Christmas (Yes!)
今年  礼物不再是煤 (好!)
Santa took me off the naughty list (Woo-hoo!)
终于把我移出了名单 (呜-呼!)
I might keep it up because it's really not so bad
我会继续做因为这样真的不难
So Santa, just bring presents
请只管给我礼物
Please, dear Santa, no more lessons
老人  我已受够了教训
Next year, Santa, just bring presents, I insist!
明年  老人  直接带礼物就行
Seriously
我没开玩笑
翻译
轮回
润色
左岸
校对
森林金雨
背景图绘制
月魇
时间轴
蛟龙  Loadhe
制作
习成 PBU 工作组
感谢观看